Guide to the Collection of Advertisements that Depict American History
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- 2010 Acquisition, 1870-1994; Series II; 284
  - Printed Ephemera
    - Serials
      - Ediciones Marco, Sitting-Bull, El Ultimo Piel Rosa (Sitting Bull, The Last Redskin)
        - No. 16, Una Audaz Aventura de Sitting-Bull (A Daring Adventure of Sitting-Bull), circa 1945 (Box 13, Folder 405)
        - No. 20, La Avalancha de Los Arikaras (The Avalanche of the Arikara), circa 1945 (Box 13, Folder 406)
      - F. Granada y Ca., Sitting Bull, el Último Sioux (Sitting Bull, The Last Sioux)
        - No. 1, A La Conquista del Valle de Oro (A Battle for the Golden Valley), circa 1909 (Box 13, Folder 407)
        - No. 2, El Bisonte Blanco de Sitting-Bull (The White Bison of Sitting-Bull), circa 1909 (Box 13, Folder 408)
        - No. 3, El Jinete Fantasma de Las Praderas (The Ghost Rider of the Plains), circa 1909 (Box 13, Folder 409)
        - No. 4, Los Squatters Misteriosos del Powder-River (The Mystery Squatters of Powder-River), circa 1909 (Box 13, Folder 410)
        - No. 5, El Demonio del Alcohol (The Demon Alcohol), circa 1909 (Box 13, Folder 411)
        - No. 6, La Marcha al Abismo (The March to the Abyss), circa 1909 (Box 13, Folder 412)
        - No. 7, El Ataque del Fuerte Lincoln (Attack on Fort Lincoln), circa 1909 (Box 13, Folder 413)
        - No. 8, La Cabaña Sospechosa (The Suspicious Cabin), circa 1909 (Box 13, Folder 414)
        - No. 9, La Princesa de las Rocas Fantásticas (The Princess of the Fantastic Rocks), circa 1909 (Box 13, Folder 415)
        - No. 10, El Tigre Negro (The Black Tiger), circa 1909 (Box 13, Folder 416)
        - No. 11, El Secreto de la Colina del Templo (The Secret of Temple Hill), circa 1909 (Box 13, Folder 417)
        - No. 12, El Valle de Los Muertos (The Valley of the Dead), circa 1909 (Box 13, Folder 418)
        - No. 13, Las Cazadores de Cabelleras (The Hunters of Scalps), circa 1909 (Box 13, Folder 419)
        - No. 14, El Los Confines de la Frontera India (On the Border of the Indian Frontier), circa 1909 (Box 13, Folder 420)
        - No. 15, Los Corsarios de la Pradera (The Corsairs of the Prairie), circa 1909 (Box 13, Folder 421)
        - No. 16, Los Espectros del Bosque de Los Muertos (The Ghosts of the Forest of the Dead), circa 1909 (Box 13, Folder 422)
        - No. 17, La Bandera del Fuerte Devils-Hill (The Flag of Fort-Hill Devils), circa 1909 (Box 13, Folder 423)
        - No. 18, El Sacraficio Funerario de Los Indios Lipanes (The Sacrificial Tomb of Lipan Indians), circa 1909 (Box 13, Folder 424)
        - No. 19, El Salteador de Diligencias (The Brigand Proceedings), circa 1909 (Box 13, Folder 425)
        - No. 20, La Traición de Flor de Púrpura (The Treason of Purple Flower), circa 1909 (Box 13, Folder 426)
        - No. 21, El Terror del Fuerte Black-Water (The Terror of Strong Black-Water), circa 1909 (Box 13, Folder 427)
        - No. 22, La Posada Sangrienta del Paso del Hechicero (The Bloody Inn and the Sorcerer's Pass), circa 1909 (Box 13, Folder 428)
        - No. 23, Sitting-Bull, El Rey de Los Tiradores (Sitting-Bull, The King of Snipers), circa 1909 (Box 13, Folder 429)
        - No. 24, Los Tiranos del Fuerte Sagamore (The Tyrants of Fort Sagamore), circa 1909 (Box 13, Folder 430)
        - No. 25, La Carrera Mortal en la Pradera (Deadly Race on the Prairie), circa 1909 (Box 13, Folder 431)
        - No. 26, Los Raptores de Jóvenes de Balls Bluff (Raptors of Youth at Balls Bluff), circa 1909 (Box 13, Folder 432)
        - No. 27, La Wolvern-Store del Missouri (The Wolvern-Store of Missouri), circa 1909 (Box 13, Folder 433)
        - No. 28, El Centro Perdido del Jefe (The Chief Lost Center), circa 1909 (Box 13, Folder 434)
        - No. 29, El Desperado del Valle de Yosémite (The Desperado of the Yosemite Valley), circa 1909 (Box 13, Folder 435)
        - No. 30, El Estanque Sospechoso de Los Castores (The Suspicious Beaver Pond), circa 1909 (Box 13, Folder 436)
        - No. 31, El Plan de Campaña Robado (The Plan of the Stolen Campaign), circa 1909 (Box 13, Folder 437)
        - No. 32, El Demonio de Hierro de Los Rostros Pálidos (The Iron Devil of the Pale Faces), circa 1909 (Box 13, Folder 438)
        - No. 33, El Puente del Diablo del Bighorn-River (Devil's Bridge at the Bighorn River), circa 1909 (Box 13, Folder 439)
        - No. 34, En la Pradera Incendiada (In the Burning Prairie), circa 1909 (Box 13, Folder 440)
        - No. 35, El Tesoro de Guerra de Los Sioux (The War Treasure of the Sioux), circa 1909 (Box 13, Folder 441)
        - No. 36, Sitting-Bull en el Lazo de la Muerte (Sitting-Bull in the Loop of Death), circa 1909 (Box 13, Folder 442)